<resources>
    <!-- Title for the application. [CHAR LIMIT=12] -->
    <string name="app_name">Venice Beach, Florida</string>

    <!-- Category name for beaches -->
    <string name="category_beaches">Beaches</string>

    <!-- Category name for hotels -->
    <string name="category_hotels">Hotels</string>

    <!-- Category name for restaurants -->
    <string name="category_restaurants">Restaurants</string>

    <!-- Category name for coffee -->
    <string name="category_coffee">Coffee</string>

    <string name="beach1">Brohard  Paw Park: For dog lovers, noteworthy in Venice is The Brohard Paw Park (1600 Harbor Dr. S., 941-861-9830), with dog drinking fountains, showers on decks for dogs only, fire hydrants and leash posts. The park is also adjacent to the only beach area in the county where dogs are allowed to roam free. Dog lovers have declared this park and beach to be the best dog friendly park in the state.</string>
    <string name="beach2">Caspersen Beach: The longest beach in Sarasota County, is located south of Venice Airport on Harbor Drive. It has been left in its natural state, uncultivated, windswept, and secluded. This is an exceptionally good area to look for and find pre-historic sharks teeth as well as enjoyable shelling. It is also site of the annual Sharks Tooth and Seafood Festival.</string>
    <string name="beach3">Venice Municipal Beach: An excellent place to find sharks teeth and other fossilized material and attracts divers to its coral reef about one quarter mile offshore.</string>
    <string name="beach4">Nokomis Beach: a quiet, family-oriented beach, a good place for fishing, strolling, or launching a boat. </string>

    <string name="restaurant1">Joseph\'\s Diner and Pizza - Authentic Italian American Cuisine. The Prendi Family welcomes you to the wonderful world of tantalizing flavors and homemade dishes that bring warmth to the heart, and smiles to all who come to enjoy. It starts with the freshest ingredients and the pride that comes with making all of our dishes from scratch.</string>
    <string name="restaurant2">Fins at Sharkey\'\s - A coastal contemporary establishment with cuisine as superb as the pristine views of the sparkling Gulf.</string>
    <string name="restaurant3">Norma Jean\'\s Sports Grill - When food, fun, and entertainment are the order of the day, Norma Jean\'\'s is where you want to be.</string>
    <string name="restaurant4">Popi\'\s Place - Popi\'\s Place Family Restaurants is one of the few remaining Florida restaurants that is chef-family owned and operated (since 1983). Your meal is about to be prepared and served as it would have been several decades ago. It is our pleasure to serve you.</string>

    <string name="hotel1">Tropical Shores Beach Resort: Rated Very High
                Midscale, smoke-free, Siesta Key hotel near beach
                2 floors, 72 rooms and suites - no elevator
                2 heated outdoor swimming pools
                Kitchen in every room
                Not pet friendly - no pets allowed
                Note: This hotel charges a resort fee of $10 per night - includes parking, Internet access, and beach amenities.</string>
    <string name="hotel2">Home2 Suites by Hilton: Modern hotel for the savvy, sophisticated traveler looking for fun and relaxation, make Home2 Suites by Hilton Nokomis your Home2.</string>
    <string name="hotel3">Comfort Suites Sarasota Key: If you\’\re looking for a spacious all-suite hotel in Sarasota, FL, remember you can get a great night\’\s rest here with us!</string>
    <string name="hotel4">Ramada by Wyndham: Soak Up the Sun
                Plan your stay at our pet-friendly Venice hotel near the beaches
                Discover exceptional amenities in the Shark Tooth Capital of the World at our Ramada Venice Hotel Venezia. Located minutes from white sandy beaches on the Gulf Coast of Florida, find easy access to the area\’\s best attractions, golf courses, shops, and restaurants when you stay at our breathtaking Venice beach setting.</string>

    <string name="coffee1">Island Coffee: Homemade bakery, breakfast and lunch. Organic Locally roasted coffee. Love what you eat and the people that serve you. This local coffee house and cafe is the "Cheers" of Venice.</string>
    <string name="coffee2">Coffee Cafe: Specializing in fresh-baked quiche, omelettes, homemade soups,salads,hot-pressed paninis,sandwiches, New York Bagels, Pastries, muffins, sweets and fresh baked Bavarian bread. Gluten-free options.
Fresh-ground coffee, Espresso drinks, Iced Coffee, All Natural Fresh-Brewed iced teas and hot teas. Chai Tea Lattes and much more!</string>
    <string name="coffee3">Menotti\'\s Coffee Stop: At Menotti\'\s Coffee Stop, you can enjoy a prime view of the Venice Beach boardwalk while you sip your morning coffee. Our coffee shop is a popular gathering spot with a relaxed, beach-front atmosphere. With both vegan and organic coffee options on our menu, our cafe attracts a range of both regulars and day-trippers.</string>
    <string name="coffee4">Black Gold Coffee Roasters: Black Gold Coffee Roasters, founded by Gary Lauters II, a highly recognized roast master who has spent nearly his entire life dedicated to and focused on coffee and the business that it has become, is truly dedicated to enriching the entire line of people involved in bringing their specially roasted coffee to the lips of the coffee lover in America. </string>

</resources>
